SANNY DEUJI 390018

Government office junior accountant with 6+ Month and UDC and LDC with 4+ years of experience finding efficiencies in busy offices. I have good computer knowledge and 50+ typing speed, Sr. Representative, Opretion at Concentrix Service Pvt. Ltd. for a strong Communication skill and good attitude.



Experience

March, 2023

November, 2022 - Concentrix Services India Private Limited Sr. Representative, Operations

Manage inbound sales inquiries related to products and Regularly exceed targets related to call volume, sales conversion, and customer satisfaction by building relationships with clients Utilize in-depth product knowledge to answer customer queries regarding products, shipping, ingredients, potential allergens, and order placement

October, 2021 -March, 2022

Collector Office, Diu | Junior Accountant

Reviewed financial documents to verify accounting data and mathematical accuracy.

Suggested key budgetary changes and preparation to final budget action plan.

Created spreadsheets using Microsoft Excel for daily, weekly and monthly reporting

April, 2020 -September, 2021

Mamlatdar Office, Diu | Upper Division

I worked with people to understand my needs and provide excellent service, Being aware of government schemes and giving benefits to the people of the village.

Worked to maintain outstanding attendance records, consistently arriving to work ready to start immediately.

Created spreadsheets using Microsoft Excel for daily, weekly and monthly reporting.



Contact Me

- 8153883636/8000083869
- sannysolanki555@gmail.com
- Karelibargh Vadodara ,India
- linkedin.com/sanny-deuji
- twitter.com/@sannysolankid

Awards

Swachhata Grahi Award, 2019

Skills

Self Motivated, Business Administration, Multitasking Ability, Hard Working, Excellent communication and Management.

Languages English, Hindi, Gujarati

Interest Music, Travelling, Painting, Cooking

June, 2017 -March, 2020

Zolawadi Village Panchayat, Diu | Lower Division Clerk

Online registration of birth and death, Correction. Maintain purchase and expenditures, preparation of development work estimates.

Created spreadsheets using Microsoft Excel for daily, weekly and monthly reporting.

To oversee the various schemes organized by the government and to inform the village people about them and to give their benefits.

I worked flexible hours across night, weekend and holiday shifts.

Manage to all accounts, register, file files etc..



Education

2017 - 2018 Saurashtra University, Rajkot | Master Of

Commerce

69.10% with First Class

May, 2017 -August, 2017 Krity Computer Academy | CCC+ With MS-OFFICE

95.5% with First Class

June, 2013 -March, 2016 Diu College, Diu | Bachelor Of Commerce

66.25% with First Class

June, 2012 -March, 2013 Gujarat Secondary & Higher Secondary Education Board, Gandhinagar | Higher Secondary Certificate

71.71% with First Class